Hey everyone! So a few weeks ago I initiated an Ask Me Anything on Instagram
and I'm going to answer the most interesting and frequent questions now
in this video. Alright, so just the basic ground. I'm 28. My birthday is in the
middle of May I'm 173 centimeters tall I don't know why a lot of people ask me
how tall I am by the way so yeah I live in Germany that was the next question
what I like to eat for breakfast pancakes I eat pancakes like every time
doesn't matter how, doesn't matter what time it is. My hobbies are well making a
lot of pictures obviously, reading a lot, I used to do horseback riding and music
stuff and I like to play a lot of games so I like to go on concerts and on
festivals I like to bake like cakes baking okay um yeah my music taste is
goth music metal music all that kind of stuff so I prefer black metal and death
metal and all kinds of gothic there have been a lot of questions about my shoes
like my favorite pair of heels or how many pairs of boots do you have and my
highest heels. And here's a video of my shoe collection. As you can see I own a
lot of daily basic shoes but also some pleaser heels which I wear for photo
shootings and catwalks. This is my most trusted pair on the right hand. Just
plain black and it fits for everything. I also got some shoes from Bands and I
have a lot of Demonio shoes because they're really comfy, they're really good
looking for all kinds of festivals and concerts and they just fit like
everything. By the way if you want to support me and support my pictures I have
Amazon wishlist and I put the link down below in the description box so if you
want to I know send me Christmas gift or something just click on the link so if I
play an instrument I used to play this thingy here is the Traverse flute
I'm not going to play now. No. So next question is how I spend my day. Well usually I get up in the
morning and go to work and work for like eight hours. Drive home and I don't know
watch some TV, read something and go to bed. It's pretty boring I know. My zodiac sign is
Taurus although I don't give a damn about zodiac signs sorry if I sell
pictures or videos no I don't if I do I speak French ah well I used to learn
French in school for like seven years but I really don't speak French if you try me
but I speak better Dutch than French. So a lot of people ask me where I used to travel.
Well, I've been to Spain, to Greece, to Australia, to Italy, to I don't know, the Netherlands of course,
Belgium, I said Austria. I've not been to Switzerland yet. I don't know why,
It just never really went that way.
What kind of car I drive?
Well, I always say it's small and red and that's enough for me because I'm not into cars.
And there's a really weird question about which bathing suit I like most.
And it's the one from... what's it? Disturbia or something.
Okay, now to the more detailed questions.
The question was what is the nerdiest thing I own?
And I probably have to admit it's my wand.
I have a wand.
Tada!
From Luna.
And I also made a latex bodysuit with the Hogwarts logo and I think it's pretty nerdy.
I guess I also got some makeup brushes in different kinds of wands from Harry Potter.
Voldemort's wand and the trick's wand and other ones so I'm pretty into Harry
Potter as you may have noticed and it drives other people nuts okay one of my
favorite questions does Olaf from frozen the Disney movie have a carrot nose or a
nose carrot. I think it's pretty awesome and I think he has a nose carrot because
he obviously needs a nose and what's more handy for snowman than a carrot as a nose?
Because I don't know, if it only would be carrot then he could be breathing through
it so it has to be in the shape of a carrot. Right? My favorite festival in
Europe? I have to say I've not been to festivals out of Germany so well I go
the WGT, the Wave Gothic Treffen in Leipzig and the Amphifestival and the
Summer Breeze Festival but the Summer Breeze is pretty metal and the Wave Gothic
Treffen in Leipzig is just a week of camping and seeing awesome bands.
Since I'm into gothic and metal music these are the ones I prefer.
If I could choose a fictional world to live in, which would it be?
Well, I think it's obvious it would be like the Harry Potter world, because I think it's awesome!
Okay, enough Harry Potter references now.
Alright, let's move on.
When did you start being a photo model?
Well, I started standing in front of cameras when I was 17.
So I'm now 28, you can do the math by yourself.
I started to do some random photo shootings like portraits and fashion stuff.
I only recently started with the alternative fashion, well not recently but like the last
four years.
So out of the over ten years I'm standing in front of cameras I'm only doing four years
of alternative fashion and latex stuff.
And I don't earn any money with it.
I'm not a professional model, I'm not doing this for a job.
I have a job and I earn my money with something completely different and I'm just doing
this for fun and also this YouTube stuff is just fun. For my day job I'm working
as head of communication or you might call it as well social media consultant,
social media manager, PR manager for a German beverage company which makes
cider pretty tasty cider.
Best three board games I've ever played. Well, I've picked my favorite three board games
First one is this
I'm recently playing this a lot. It's Pandemic Legacy. It's a legacy game and
You have to save the world from a pandemic disease
One of my
favorite board games is Cash and Guns. It's inspired by Tarantino's Reservoir Dogs and
it's just like a party fun game and you have to play with toy form guns and it's really
the best if you're starting to get drunk or if you're drunk. It's super fun, it's super
short lived and I just like this game. It's pretty old as you may see.
Oh, I don't get this anymore.
How does it work?
And my third favorite board game is this one. It's pretty heavy. It's 10 kilogram of game material.
I just don't have any muscles because I don't work out. It's called Gloom Maiden. It's a... sorry.
It's a roleplay inspired tabletop game and I think we played like 50 hours this year
and we've not even covered half of the game.
Somehow this question is asked all the time when I'm doing an ask me anything.
Pineapple on pizza, yes or no?
know. Yes, I love pineapple on pizza. I love pineapple everywhere. Toast on pizza, like,
everywhere. I don't know. I just love it. My favorite Supergirl movie? I don't know. I've
not seen any Supergirl movie. I'm not that much into Marvel or DC. Do the modeling gigs pay you?
No, they don't. I don't do any pay shootings, because I like to just keep it as a hobby.
Like I said, I'm not earning money with this. I started working with companies together and they
sent me items which I use for photoshootings so I can provide you guys with new pictures and new
outfits and yeah I provide them with good pictures, I hope so, to post and this is the kind of
collaborations I do but not for money have you ever played clash of clans I
don't think so do you play Dungeons and Dragons no I only play Midgard as pen
and paper my favorite computer game I don't play that many computer games I
split Dragon Age and I like them pretty much what was your craziest photo
location? Well I've been to Australia last year and that was pretty awesome. I
shooted at a waterfall site and at a beach and right in the heart of Sydney
at the Opera and stuff like that. That was pretty awesome and I've been to
Nullarney which is a German isle just a few months back and it was pretty
exhausting and pretty cold and one day you had to get up at 4.30 in the morning
because we want to do a sunrise shooting and surprise the Sun was not there when
we got on top of the dunes but we did some pictures anyway and it's been a
great experience and I love the pictures that came out of it and I think these
These are the two most craziest photo occasions I've been to.
Your guilty pleasure music?
I guess that's Ylvis.
They're brothers, they're from Norway and they're just hilarious.
I don't know.
I love their music to pieces.
They're just making esoteric songs from every genre and it's so much fun.
have to check them out. Did you aspire to have such a large following or was it
something that surprised you? Yes it did surprise me. I didn't think it would go
that far. Like one and a half years ago I had 10k followers on Instagram and now
it's over 100k which is pretty high for my small niche of a fetish or alternative
clothing scene and what was your best moment in your modeling career and I
have to say some of them happened this year because I've been the cover model
of Amelke Dista it's an alternative fashion show in Munich Germany and I've
not been just a cover model of the event I've also could be seen in like the My King volume and also in
Marky with this picture and I've been on the cover of My King this month
which is a pretty big deal and of course on the lookbook from avant-gardista and this is so cool
because something I can like touch or like look at it in real life what are your favorite your
future business goals or plans I don't know I'll see what's the most exotic piece in my wardrobe
Well, it is this corset from AMF. It's a German artist from Berlin and it's like
real beauty. It's hand painted and hand crafted and yeah I ordered it in this
style with the white and blue it's called frozen and I just love the ribs
being visible and stuff like that so this is it I just put it on for a second
it's not really tie-laced but I think it looks awesome and I have to admit I
I bought it when I was pretty drunk at last year's VGT festival in Leipzig.
But I just love it.
And yeah, I think it's really cool.
Okay, another modeling question.
How much international model work do you do?
I don't do any international model work.
I've worked for AMF corsets in the Netherlands, in Amsterdam at the Wasteland Party.
That was the most international work I've done because as I said it's just a hobby.
If someone wants to pay me to travel to their country and do shooting there, just talk to
me.
But yeah, I like to be on catwalks.
I've worked for Pandora Deluxe and a lot of designers, Romie Couture. I don't know, I had to look it up because it's been a lot of runway shows during the last few years.
Yeah, just hit me message if you want to know more about this.
Best book of 2019. I recently started to read Leith Baldugo or whatever he or she is called.
and I loved her novels. I'm into fantasy novels a lot so yeah all that stuff.
What's the best piece of life advice you can give? Well I think I'm not in a
position to give life advice. I just like to live my own life and the kind of do
what makes you happy. Like really makes you happy. Choose a job that makes you
happy and choose a private life that makes you happy and I think this is going to be the most
you can make out of your life what is your favorite place that you always wanted to visit
well I've got a few on my bucket list something like seeing the northern lights although it would
be pretty cold and I despise the cold and just like more with summer vacation person favorite
countries food I really into Asian food and I really like pizza on every
occasion so that was it thanks for asking all those questions I hope you do
know me a bit better by now and if you liked it click on the subscribe button
button and yeah just watch my other videos and like this one I really
appreciate it thanks for watching and have a nice day